

INFO



Email adalu.rammo@gmail.com

in LinkedIn /in/adaluramirez

GitHub github.com/adaramirez

SOFT SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Professional liability
- Agile Environment
- Critical Thinking
- Self Learning

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- JavaScript
- CSS
- HTML5
- GitHub

ADA RAMIREZ

JUNIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I am an intrepid professional photographer who decided to make a 180-degree change, entering to a programming bootcamp. JavaScript was the chosen language to be the first one, I found out that in order to learn it, you also need a lot of creativity, just focused differently. In other words, learning a programming language is like a camera, you focus on what is important (the requirements you need to solve), capture the good time (the functions that actually worked), develop from the negative (all the mistakes you made in order to solve the problem), and if things don't work out, just take another shot (one more try, this is your code).

WORK EXPERIENCE

Bilingual Interpreter

Human Quality 2016-2017 Outsourcing company that worked for Language Line Corporation. Interpreting calls between only English speaking persons and only Spanish speaking persons for different companies, such as banks, insurances, 911, government institutions, schools and others.

Customer Service Representative

TeleTech 2012-2013

Customer Service Calls for Bank of America in English and Spanish.

EDUCATION EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer Jr. Laboratoria 2018-2018 6 months bootcamp to learn JavaScript, HTML, CSS, jQuery and other programming tools to become a Junior Front End Developer.

Bachelor of Visual Arts Universidad de Guadalajara 2012-2015 Major: Photography

Associates in Arts Tarrant County College 2008-2009 Phi Tetha Kappa International Honor Society